https://www.mrboots.com/privacy-policy-pg-2.html

www.mrboots.com
Call Us:  412-823-3210
Email Us:  info-at-mrboots-dot-com
Western Store - Boots Hats Belts Buckles - Free Shipping on orders of $100 - USA only.
My Account
Quick Find:
Categories
Western Accessories (125)
Western Belts (121)
Western Boots (433)
Western Buckles (417)
Western Apparel (405)
Western Hats (239)
Western Home Decor (22)
Western Jewelry (98)
Kids Corral (150)
Dance Items (447)
Gift Certificate
Clearance and Sale Items (49)
Hot Information
Categories
Please SelectWestern Accessories  Bags  Briefcases  Cell Phone Cases  Pet Collars  Dream Catchers  Flags  Luggage  Purses    Pouch Bags    Purses and Bags    Saddle Purses and More    Blazin Roxx Purses    Other  Totes  Wallets Ladies  Wallets Mens    Bifold Wallets    Trifold Wallets    Trucker Wallets    Rodeo Wallets    Money Clips  Gun Belts and Holsters  Auto and Truck    License Plates    Trailer Hitch Covers    Signs    Accessories and More  OtherWestern Belts  Ladies Belts    Ladies Concho Belts    Ladies Fashion Belts    Ladies Rhinestone Belts    Ladies Western Belts  Mens Belts    Made in the USA    Mens Concho Belts    Mens Fashion Belts    Tooled Embossed Leather Belts    Ranger Belts    Western Classic Belts    Casual Belts    Exotic Leather    Suspenders  Kids Belts    Boys Belts    Girls BeltsWestern Boots  Ladies Boots    Ladies Exotic Boots    Ladies Laced Boots    Ladies Roper Boots    Ladies Western Boots    Ladies Gypsy Collection    Ladies Casual Footwear    Ladies English Riding Boots    Ladies Rain Mud Boots    Ladies Slippers    Ladies Dance Boots  Mens Boots    Mens Western Boots    Mens Roper Boots    Mens Exotic Boots    Mens Work Boots    Mens Motorcycle Boots    Mens Footwear  Kids Boots    Infant Boots    Boys Toddler Boots    Girls Toddler Fashion Boots    Childrens Boots    Youth Boots    Kids English Riding Boots    Kids Sandles    Kids Slippers    Kids Clearance Boots  Boot Accessories    Boot Bags Shoe Bags    Boot Bolos    Boot Bracelets    Boot Bling    Boot Candy    Boot Straps Boot Chains      Design Your Own    Boot Tips    Boot Heel Guards    Kilties    Western Spurs and Straps      Silver Chrome Stainless Steel      Colored Spurs      Jingle Bob Spurs      Spur Straps  Boot and Leather Care Products    Suede and Nubuck Care    Brushes Applicators Shine Cloths    Boot Care Kits    Polish and Dressings    Repair Products    Waterproofing    Kiwi Camp Dry Products    Cleaners Conditioners    Oil Tanned Leather Care    Exotic Leather Products    Other Boot Care Products  Boot Socks Insoles Laces Jacks    Boot and Shoe Horns    Boot and Shoe Laces    Boot and Shoe Trees    Boot Dryers    Boot Hooks    Boot Jacks    Boot Savers    Boot Shapers    Boot Socks      Ladies Socks      Mens Socks      Kids Socks    Insoles and Arch SupportsWestern Buckles  Buckle Sets    1/2 inch    3/4 inch    1 inch    1-1/4 inch    1-1/2 inch  Butterfly Buckles  Car Buckles  Cowboy Rodeo Buckles  Cowgirl Rodeo Buckles  Cross Buckles  Custom Engraved Trophy Buckles  Custom Trophy Buckles  Eagle Buckles  Farm Equipment Buckles  Graffiti Buckles  Gun Buckles  Heart Buckles  Horse Buckles  Initial Buckles  Kids Buckles  Lightning Ridge Trophy Buckles  MLB Buckles  Motorcycle Buckles  Music and Dancing Buckles  NASCAR Racing Buckles  Native American Buckles  NCAA Buckles  NFL Buckles  NHL Buckles  Outdoors Buckles  Oval Buckles  Patriotic Buckles  Places Countries Cities  Rectangular Buckles  Redneck Buckles  Religious Buckles  Rhinestones Bling Buckles  Southern Pride Buckles  Special and Unique Designs  States  Trades Professions Buckles  Trophy Buckles  Trucking and Trucks  Whiskey and Alcohol  WolvesWestern Apparel  Ladies Apparel    Ladies Western
Shirts    Ladies Tank Tops      LT Cowgirls      LT Horses      LT Music      LT Native American      LT Outdoors      LT Patriotic      LT Southern Pride      LT Wolves    Ladies T-Shirts      LTS Outdoors      LTS Cowgirls      LTS Horses      LTS International Harvester      LTS Music      LTS Native American      LTS Patriotic      LTS Southern Pride      LTS Wolves    Ladies Sweatshirts      LSW Outdoors      LSW Cowgirls      LSW Horses      LSW Music      LSW Native American      LSW Southern Pride      LSW Wolves    Ladies Hoodies      LHD Outdoors      LHD Cowgirls      LHD Horses      LHD Music      LHD Native American      LHD Southern Pride      LHD Wolves    Ladies Outerwear    Ladies Long Johns  Mens Apparel    Mens Western Shirts    Mens Western Fashion Shirts    Mens T-Shirts      MTS Animals Outdoors Wildlife      MTS Cowboy Rodeo Western      MTS Horses      MTS International Harvester      MTS Music      MTS Native American      MTS Patriotic      MTS Southern Pride      MTS Trucks      MTS Wolves    Mens Sweatshirts      MSW Animals Outdoors Wildlife      MSW Cowboy Rodeo Western      MSW Horses      MSW Music      MSW Native American      MSW Patriotic      MSW Southern Pride      MSW Trucks      MSW Wolves    Mens Hoodies      MHD Outdoors      MHD Cowboy      MHD Horses      MHD Music      MHD Native American      MHD Patriotic      MHD Southern Pride      MHD Trucks      MHD Wolves    Mens Vests    Mens Outerwear      Mens Duster and Slickers      Mens Chaps    Mens Long Johns  Kids Apparel    Boys Shirts    Girls Shirts    Girls Outfits    Infant Toddler Apparel    Kids Chaps and Vests    Kids T-Shirts      KTS Outdoors      KTS Cowboy Rodeo Western      KTS Cowgirl Rodeo Western      KTS Horses      KTS Music      KTS Native American      KTS Patriotic      KTS Southern Pride      KTS Trucks      KTS Wolves    Kids Sweatshirts      KSW Outdoors      KSW Cowboy      KSW Cowgirl      KSW Horses      KSW Music      KSW Native American      KSW Patriotic      KSW Southern Pride      KSW Wolves    Kids Hoodies      KHD Outdoors      KHD Cowboy      KHD Cowgirl      KHD Horses      KHD Music      KHD Native American      KHD Patriotic      KHD Southern Pride      KHD Wolves    Kids Long Johns    Kids Outerwear  Cowboy Scarves and Western Ties    Bandanas    Cowboy Wild Rags    Western Bolo Ties      Arrowheads      Bulls and Buffalo      Circular Oval Triangular      Eagles      Clubs Organizations      Horses      Initials      Ladies      Music Dancing      Native American      Patriotic Armed Forces      Religious      Rodeo Cowboys Western      Southwestern      Southern Pride      Texas      Unique Designs and Shapes      Wolves Outdoors    Western Scarf Slides    Western Scarf Ties    Western Ties  Apparel Accessories    Badges    Collar Tips    Conchos    Cuff Links    Patches    Gloves    OtherWestern Hats  Adult Hats and Caps    Camo Hats    Crushable Hats    Felt Hats    Fashion Straw Hats    Straw Hats    Leather Hats    Novelty Hats    Outdoors Hats    Ladies Hats    Ball Caps Fashion Caps      Farm Boy      John Deere      Ariat      Camo      Justin      Ladies      PBR      Southern Pride Rebel Redneck      Western      Other    Headwraps  Kids Hats and Caps    Kids Caps    Kids Western Hats  Hat Accessories    Cowboy Hat Bands      Bone Bead Hat Bands      Camo Hat Bands      Leather Hat Bands      Classic Hat Bands      Concho Hat Bands      Economy Hat Bands      Exotic Leather Hat Bands      Feather Hat Bands      Horse Hair Hat Bands      Rhinestone Hat Bands    Stampede Strings    Hat Care Products    Hat Pins    Tiaras and CrownsWestern Home Decor  Accessories    Figurines    Photo Albums    Book Ends    Candles    Clocks    Mirrors    Office    Picture Frames    Statues    Throws Blankets    Trinket Boxes    Wastebaskets    Other  Bed and Bath  Books  Kitchen  Lighting  Outdoor Garden  Wall Decor    Hooks    Coat Racks    Signs    OtherWestern Jewelry  Add A Charm  Barrettes  Bracelets  Chokers  Earrings  Earring and Necklace Sets  Hair Accessories  Head Bands  Key Rings Key Chains  Money Clips  Necklaces  Pins  Rings  Sale ItemsKids Corral  Western Clothing    Boys Shirts    Girls Shirts    Girls Outfits    Infant and Toddler    Chaps Vests    T-Shirts      Animals Outdoors Wildlife      Cowboys Rodeo Western      Cowgirls Rodeo Western      Horses      Music      Native American      Patriotic      Southern Pride Rebel Redneck      Trucking - Trucks      Wolves    Sweatshirts      Animals Outdoors Wildlife      Cowboys Rodeo Western      Cowgirls Rodeo Western      Horses      Music      Native American      Patriotic      Southern Pride Rebel Redneck      Wolves    Hoodies      Animals Outdoors Wildlife      Cowboys Rodeo Western      Cowgirls Rodeo Western      Horses      Music      Native American      Patriotic      Southern Pride Rebel Redneck      Wolves    Long Johns    Outerwear    Bolo Ties  Boots    Clearance    Infant    Boys Toddler Boots    Children    Youth    English Riding    Slippers    Socks  Belts    Boys    Girls  Buckles  Western Hats and Caps    Western Hats    Caps  Accessories    Bags,
Backpacks    Luggage    Purses    Totes    Wallets    Other  Western Toys    Action Figures Playsets    Sporting Goods    Stuffed Animals    Guns Holsters    Ropin Sets    Stick Horses    OtherDance Items  Dance Accessories  Dance Boots    Ladies Dance Boots    Mens Dance Boots    Dance Boot Sale  Dance Shoes    Ladies Dance Shoes      Closed Toe        Flat Heel        Cuban Heel Low        Cuban Heel Mid        Cuban Heel Thick        High Heel to 2 Inch        High Heel to 3 Inch      Open Toe        Cuban Heel Low        Cuban Heel Mid        Cuban Heel Thick        High Heel          Beige Brown Flesh Tan          Blue Purple          Black          Gold          Print          Red          Silver          White        Competitive Dancer        Tango Heel      Ladies Swing      West Coast Swing      Wedding      Dance Sneakers      Clearance Sale Items    Mens Dance Shoes      Standard Heel      Latin Heel      Mens Swing      Mens Dance Sneakers    Girls Dance Shoes    Boys Dance ShoesGift CertificateClearance and Sale Items  Apparel    Kids    Ladies    Mens  Belts    Kids    Ladies    Mens  Bolo Ties  Buckles  Evenin Star Dance Boots    Ladies    Mens  Home Decor  Jewelry  Ladies Dance Shoes  Mens Dance Shoes  Tic Tac Toes Dance Boots  Toys  Western Boots Plus    Boot Accessories    Kids Boots    Ladies Boots Plus    Mens Boots Plus  Western Hats
Suppliers
Please SelectAlmaxAriatAris AllenAtsko, IncAustin AccentBickmoreBlazin RoxxBoot CandyBoot DoctorBrushy Creek Belt and Buckle CoBullhide Hat Co.Cactus MountainCadillac Shoe ProductsChippewa BootsCrumrine Buckle CompanyDouble BarrelDouble SEclectic Products, Inc.Evenin' Star Boot Co.Farm Boy BrandFarm Girl BrandFashion West AccessoriesFiebing CompanyHD XtremeHickory BrandsJ.R. PalaciosJ.T. FooteJohn Deere Licensed ProductJT InternationalJustinJustin AccessoriesJustin Boot CareJustin BootsJustin Boots HeadwearJustin SilverKellyKiddie Korral CompanyKiwiLexolLightning RidgeLos AltosM and F WesternM.R. BootsMeltonianMR. BootsNocona Belt Co.Old West JamaOutback Trading CompanyPedagRhinestone Jewelry Corp.Rochester Shoe Tree CoRoper ApparelRoper FootwearRoyal KingSage Boot CompanyScout Boot CareSedona WestSilver Creek by Leegin LeatherSiskiyou GiftsSole Choice, Inc.Star Brush CompanyTandy Leather CompanyThe Boot DoctorTic-Tac-ToesTOPPERSTough 1TwisterVery Fine Dancesport ShoesWestern CharmWestern Express, Inc.Western Fashion AccessoriesWestern MomentsWyoming TradersYAK PAK
Specials
VF-1643-NB181-20 Black Nubuck and Black Mesh$69.00  $62.10
VF-1616-L630-15-SP Creamy White & White Mesh$89.00  $80.10
VF-1620-L630 White Satin with 2 Accent Buckles$69.00  $62.10
Top » Pages » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
• To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
• To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
• To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
• To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
• To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required toï¿½keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their Account and going to the 'My Account' page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at mrboots.biz.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
This policy was last modified on 11/25/2009
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
www.mrboots.com
P.O. BOX 103
TRAFFORD, PA 15085
USA
info@mrboots.com
412-823-3210
Shopping Cart
0 items
Your Account
Your Email Address
Your Password
Wishlist
My Wish List [+]
Wish List Help [?]
Shop by Price
Under $10.00
From $10.00 to $20.00
From $20.00 to $30.00
From $30.00 to $50.00
From $50.00 to $75.00
$75.00 and above
Advance Search
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.
Information
General InformationContact UsSize InformationBuckle Event Figures->Yes, we are still open for business but we closed our showroom.Showroom InformationSite MapFind us on FacebookNew ProductsLinksVendorsYES, WE ARE STILL IN BUSINESS BUT WE CLOSED OUR SHOWROOM.Search EnginesExperiencing problems with our checkout
Faq
Dance BootsDance ShoesReward Point ProgramShowroomCowboy BootsWish ListGift Certificates
